(Leonard:)Actually, it's not all that easy to find.
Yeah, really? Well, my friends at work
found it, my sister found it.
(Penny:)Judging by my e-mail, a number of prisoners
at the Michigan State Penitentiary found it.
What exactly did this guy write?
(Leonard:)Not that I need to know
the details of your sex life.
(Leonard:)I just thought...
(Leonard:)Never mind.
No, you know what?
(Penny:)Might as well read it,
everybody else has. Go ahead.
(Penny:)Oh, God, I just feel so betrayed
and embarrassed.
I just wanna crawl into a hole and die.
(Leonard:)Okay, well, you know, this isn't that bad.
(Leonard:)It just paints the picture
of a very affectionate woman...
(Leonard:)...who's open to expressing her affection
in nontraditional locales.
(Penny:)Oh, God.
Elevators, parks, movie theaters.
(Leonard:)Out of curiosity...
(Leonard:)...is this subway, the transportation system,
or Subway, the sandwich shop?